Guide to the Winterhouse Art and Design Collection of Volume 1 Number 1
Yale University Arts Library
- Examples, 1919-2011; Series II
  - Design and Culture: The Journal of the Design Studies Forum. Volume 1: Issue 1. Oxford: Berg Publishers, March 2009. pp. 156. (Box 2, Folder 60)
    Edited by Elizabeth Guffey.
    Contributions by Alice Twemlow, Johanna Drucker and Denise Gonzales-Crisp.
    Article of note: "I Can't Talk to You if You Say That."
  - Design + Sign. Volume One: Number One. New York: Fashion Institute of Technology, 1990. pp. 40. (Box 2, Folder 61)
    Edited by Richard Martin.
    Contributions by Paula Baxter and Gabriel Weisberg.
    Article of note: "Nude Men in the Midst of Dressed Women in Fashion Imagery, 1980-1990."
    Design by Marvin Hoshino.
  - De/signed. Volume 1: Issue 1. Ahmedabad, India: Patel Printing, December 2009. pp. 54. (Box 2, Folder 62)
    Edited by Vijai Singh Katiyar and Shilpa Das.
    Contributions by Bhavin Kothari, H. Kumar Vyas and Deepak John Mathew.
    Article of note: "Design Thinking and Management: Shifting Values."
    Design by Tarun Deep Girdher.
  - The Diagonal: An Illustrated Monthly Magazine Devoted to the Explanation of the Rediscovered Principles of Greek Design, Their Appearance in Nature and Their Application to the Needs of Modern Art. Number One. New Haven: Yale University Press, November 1919. pp. 24. (Box 2, Folder 63)
    Edited by Jay Hambidge.
    Article of note: "Dynamic Symmetry of the Human Figure for Advanced Students."
  - The Dial: A Magazine of Fiction. Volume 1: Issue 1. New York: Dial Press, Fall 1959. pp. 160. (Box 2, Folder 64)
    Edited by James Silberman. Contributions by T.S. Eliot, Herbert Gold and Philip Roth.
    Article of note: "Ulysses, Order and Myth."
  - Digital Processes: An International Journal on the Theory and Design of Digital Systems. Volume One: Number One. Saphorin, Switzerland: Georgi Publishing, Spring 1975. pp. 94. (Box 2, Folder 65)
    Edited by Douglas Lewin.
    Contributions by R. G. Bennetts, D. C. Brittle and J. L. Washington.
    Article of note: "A Modular Approach to Test Sequence Generation for Large Digital Networks."
  - Dissent: A Quarterly of Socialist Opinion. Volume One: Number One. New York: Dissent Publishing, Winter 1954. pp. 112. (Box 2, Folder 66)
    Edited by Travers Clement, Lewis Coser, Irving Howe, Harold Orlans, Stanley Plastrik and Meyer Schapiro.
    Contributions by Irving Howe, Rosa Luxemburg and C. Wright Mills.
    Article of note: "Government by Secrecy."
  - Dot Dot Dot: Graphic Design and Visual Culture. Number One. Leipzig, Germany: Broodje & Kaas Publishing, Spring 2000. pp. 96. (Box 2, Folder 67)
    Edited by Jurgen Albrecht, Stuart Bailey, Peter Bilak and Tom Unverzagt.
    Contributions by Paul Barnes, Max Bruinsma and Richard Hollis.
    Article of note: "Encyclopedia of 20th Century Graphic Design Periodicals."
    Design by Paul Barnes.
  - Dot Zero. Number One. New York: Unimark International, April 1966. pp. 52. (Box 2, Folder 68)
    Edited by Robert Malone and Mildred Constantine.
    Contributions by Arthur Drexler, Marshall McLuhan and Bruno Munari.
    Article of note: "Decline of the Visual."
  - DoubleTake. Volume One: Number One. Durham, North Carolina: Center for Documentary Studies at Duke University, Summer 1995. pp. 128. (Box 2, Folder 69)
    Edited by Robert Coles.
    Contributions by John Berger, Michael Lesy and Danny Lyon.
    Article of note: "Dreams by Wendy Ewald."
    Design by Molly Renda.
  - The Drawbridge. Issue One. London: Blacks, Spring 2006. pp. 4. (Box 2, Folder 70)
    Edited by Bigna Pfenninger and Mandana Ruane.
    Contributions by Tariq Ali, Gordon Brotherston and Jeff Fisher.
    Article of note: "April Hybridity."
    Design by Stephen Coates.
  - Dwell. Volume One: Number One. San Francisco: Pixie, October 2000. pp. 96. (Box 2, Folder 71)
    Edited by Karrie Jacobs.
    Contributions by Robert Cardin, Olivier Laude and Philip Nobel.
    Article of note: "The Lofting of America."
    Design by Jeanette Hodge.
  - DVA: Magazine for Visual Relations. Volume One: Number One. Slovakia. Two-part poster., undated (Box 7, Folder 245)
    Edited by Eduard Čehovin.
    Contribution by Fedja Vukić.
    Design by Eduard Čehovin.
  - EcoMag. Number 1. London: EcoLabs, Summer 2009. pp. 26. (Box 2, Folder 72)
    Edited by Jody Boehnert.
    Contributions by Airside, Leona Clark and Si Yeun Kim.
    Article of note: "Tipping Point."
    Design by Jody Boehnert.
  - Education Matters: A Journal of Opinion and Research. Volume One: Number One. Cambridge, MA: Hoover, Spring 2001. pp. 76. (Box 2, Folder 73)
    Edited by Paul E. Peterson.
    Contributions by E. D. Hirsch Jr., Caroline Hoxby and Nancy and Ted Sizer.
    Article of note: "Romancing the Child."
    Design by John Sizing.
  - EGG. Issue One. New York: EGG, March 1990. pp. 176. (Box 7, Folder 246)
    Edited by Malcolm S. Forbes and Hal Rubenstein.
    Contributions by Linda Ellerbee, William Geist and Hal Rubenstein.
    Article of note: "Smooth Talk, Strange Tastes."
    Design by Douglas Riccardi.
  - ESPN: The Magazine. Issue One. New York: ESPN, March 23, 1998. pp. 184. (Box 7, Folder 247)
    Edited by John Papanek.
    Contributions by Tom Friend, Curry Kirkpatrick and Bob Knight.
    Article of note: "The Mismatch."
    Design by F. Darrin Perry.
  - Esquire Gentleman. Issue One. New York: Hearst, Spring–Summer 1993. pp. 232. (Box 2, Folder 74)
    Edited by Woody Hochswender.
    Contributions by Bill Blass, Eric Bogosian and Phil Stern.
    Article of note: "Not a Gentlemanly Thing to Do."
    Design by Maryjane Fahey.
  - Evergreen Review. Volume One: Number One. New York: Grove Press, 1957. pp. 192. (Box 2, Folder 75)
    Edited by Barney Rosset and Donald Allen.
    Contributions by Samuel Beckett, James Purdy and Jean-Paul Sartre.
    Article of note: "After Budapest." Cover photograph by Harold Feinstein.
  - Eye: Magazine of the Yale Arts Association. Number 1. New Haven: Yale Arts Association, 1967. pp. 40. (Box 2, Folder 76)
    Edited by Marlene Marie McKinley.
    Contributions by George Kubler, Christopher Tunnard and Jack Tworkov.
    Article of note: "Aesthetics and the Urban Environment."
    Design by Bradbury Thompson.
  - Fact. Volume One: Issue One. New York: Fact Magazine, January–February 1964. pp. 64. (Box 2, Folder 77)
    Contributions by Dwight Macdonald, Mary McCarthy and Bertrand Russell.
    Article of note: "The Sexual Symbolism of Christmas."
  - Fence. Volume One: Number One. New York: Fence Magazine, Spring 1998. pp. 160. (Box 2, Folder 78)
    Edited by Rebecca Wolff.
    Contributions by Anne Carson, Stephen Dixon, Rick Moody and Paul Muldoon.
    Article of note: "Ordinary Time: Virginia Woolf and Thucydides on War."
    Design by Adam Hurwitz.
  - The Film Journal. Volume One: Number One. Roanoke, Virginia: Film Journal, Spring 1971. pp. 80. (Box 2, Folder 79)
    Edited by Thomas Atkins.
    Contributions by Jack Fisher, John Graham and Rodger Larson.
    Article of note: "Reactions to 'I Am Curious Yellow'."
    Design by Ronald Seichrist.
  - FMR: The Magazine of Franco Maria Ricci. Issue One. New York: Franco Maria Ricci, June 1984. pp. 160. (Box 2, Folder 80)
    Edited by Franco Maria Ricci.
    Contributions by David Alan Brown, Julio Cortázar and Pierre Klossowski.
    Article of note: "Aloys Zötl."
    Design by Laura Casalis.
  - FOCUS Systems Journal. Volume One: Number One. New York: Information Builders Publishing, January 1988. pp. 80. (Box 2, Folder 81)
    Edited by Russell C. Lipton.
    Contributions by Gerald D. Cohen, Claude Goldman and Michael Howard.
    Article of note: "Benchmarking The Benchmark."
    Design by Julian A. Hyman.
  - Fortune. Volume 1: Number 1. New York: Time-Fortune, February 1930. pp. 184. (Box 7, Folder 248)
    Edited by Henry R. Luce.
    Contributions by Margaret Bourke-White and Alfred Eisenstadt.
    Article of note: "Radio Corporation of America."
  - Forum: For the Problems of Zionism, World Jewry and the State of Israel. Number One. Jerusalem: World Zionist Organization, December 1953. pp. 204. (Box 2, Folder 82)
    Edited by N. Rotenstreich.
    Contributions by Isaiah Berlin, David Ben Gurion and Isaiah Wolfsberg.
    Article of note: "Jewish Slavery and Emancipation."
  - Friction: Culture, Music, Politics, Art & Sport for the Independent Minded. Number One. Akron, Ohio: Monkey Bubble Media, 2002. pp. 160. (Box 2, Folder 83)
    Edited by Melissa Hostetler.
    Contributions by D.A. Blyer, Peter Kuper and George Sanchez.
    Article of note: "Stupid and Contagious: Nirvana and the Decline of Rock Journalism."
    Design by Allen Harrison and Brendan Firem.
  - Fright and Volume. Issue 1: Volume 1. New York: Kutztown Publishing, 2006. pp. 131. (Box 2, Folder 84)
    Edited by Nicole Baker and Yasha Wallin.
    Contributions by Marcelo Gomes, Melissa Brown and Jen DeNike.
    Article of note: "Brendan Cass Interviews Donald Baechler."
    Design by Stuart Lyle.
  - Front. Number One. New York: Storefront for Art + Architecture, Fall 1987. pp. 24. (Box 2, Folder 85)
    Edited by Lebbeus Woods and Kyong Park.
    Contributions by Elizabeth Diller and Ricardo Scofidio.
    Article of note: "Bodybuildings: Architectural Facts and Fictions."
    Design by Tracey Cameron.
  - Gain: AIGA Journal of Design for the Network Economy. Volume One: Number One. New York: AIGA, 2000. pp. 36. (Box 2, Folder 86)
    Edited by David Brown.
    Contributions by Richard Buchanan, Richard Grefé and Glen Helfand.
    Article of note: "Supermodeler: Hugh Dubberly."
    Design by Sapient.
  - Gastronomica: Journal of Food and Culture. Volume One: Number One. Berkeley: University of California Press, February 2001. pp. 122. (Box 2, Folder 87)
    Edited by Darra Goldstein.
    Contributions by T. R. Durham, William Nesto and Rick Stein.
    Article of note: "Sicilian Cheese in Medieval Arab Recipes."
    Design by Frances Baca and Lee Friedman.
  - Georgetown Journal of International Affairs. Volume One: Number One. Washington, DC: Georgetown University, Winter–Spring 2000. pp. 132. (Box 2, Folder 88)
    Edited by Stephanie Kaplan and Ben Powell.
    Contributions by John Esposito, Mark Juergensmeyer and Vali Nasr.
    Article of note: "Responding to Religious Terrorism."
    Design by Miguel Buckenmeyer.
  - GOOD. Issue 001. Los Angeles: GOOD Magazine, September/October 2006. pp. 112. (Box 2, Folder 89)
    General note
    See also Box 7, Folder 249 for GOOD supplement.
    Edited by Zach Frechette.
    Contributions by 2x4, Olivier Laude and W+K12.
    Article of note: "On the Line."
    Design by Casey Caplowe.
  - GOOD Business. Beta Issue. Los Angeles: GOOD Magazine, November/December 2008. pp. 32. (Box 2, Folder 90)
    Contributions by Alex Goldmark and Luke O'Brien.
    Article of note: "The Buck Stops Where?"
  - Grand Street. Volume One: Number One. New York: Grand Street Publications, Autumn 1981. pp. 194. (Box 2, Folder 91)
    Edited by Ben Sonnenberg and Elizabeth Pochoda.
    Contributions by Northrop Frye, Ted Hughes, Alice Munro and James Salter.
    Article of note: "From The Great Code."
    Design by Deborah Thomas.
  - Graphic. Issue One. London: Bis, Spring 2003. pp. 176. (Box 3, Folder 92)
    Edited by Marc Valli.
    Contributions by Victor Cheung, Catherine Hall and Patrick Sundkvist.
    Article of note: "Experimental Jetset on Wim Crouwel."
    Design by Sebastian Campos.
  - Grey Room: Architecture, Art, Media, Politics. Number One. Cambridge, Massachusetts: MIT Press, Fall 2000. pp. 128. (Box 3, Folder 93)
    Edited by Branden Joseph, Reinhold Martin and Felicity Scott.
    Contributions by Hubert Damisch, Sylvia Lavin and Gayatri Chakravorty Spivak.
    Article of note: "Monument and Crime: The Destruction of Historic Architecture in Kosovo."
    Design by Kathleen Oginski and Greg Van Alstyne.
  - Hagar: International Social Science Review. Volume One: Number One. Beer-Sheva, Israel: Ben-Gurion University, 2000. pp. 188. (Box 3, Folder 94)
    Edited by Oren Yiftachel.
    Contributions by Valentine Moghadam, Yehouda Shenhav and Raef Zreik.
    Article of note: "On Law, Planning and the Shaping of Space."
  - The Hasty Papers: A One-Shot Review. Number One. New York: The Hasty Papers, 1960. pp. 200. (Box 7, Folder 250)
    Edited by Alfred Leslie.
    Contributions by John Ashbery, Fidel Castro, Robert Frank, Jack Kerouac, J. Robert Oppenheimer and Jean-Paul Sartre.
    Article of note: "The World Contracted to A Recognizable Image."
    Design by Marc Ratliff.
  - Hebraic Political Studies. Volume One: Number One. Jerusalem: Shalem Press, Fall 2005. pp. 136. (Box 3, Folder 95)
    Edited by Arthur Eyffinger and Gordon Schochet.
    Contributions by Silvia Berti, Steven Grosby and Kalman Neuman.
    Article of note: "The Biblical 'Nation' as a Problem of Philosophy."
  - Honest. Volume One: Issue One. New York: Honest Publications, Spring–Summer 2003. pp. 43. (Box 7, Folder 251)
    Edited by Stella Bugbee, Jon Milott and Cary Murnion.
    Contributions by Kiera Alexandra, Andrea Codrington and Damon Rich.
    Article of note: "On Locations with Gregory Crewdson."
    Design by Honest.
  - Horseshit: The Offensive Review. Number One. Hermosa Beach, California: Scum Publishing, 1965. pp. 40. (Box 3, Folder 96)
    Edited by Thomas Dunker.
    Article of note: "Support Your Loco Police, Who Enforce the Prejudices of Some People by Violating the Rights of Others."
    Design by Robert Dunker.
  - Hunt News. Volume 1: Issue 1. Falls Village, Connecticut: D. M. Hunt Library, 2010. pp. 6. (Box 3, Folder 97)
    Edited by Mary Elling, Zoë Fedorjaczenko and Sharon Hamilton.
    Article of note: "Things are Looking Up: Roof Debt Retired."
    Design by Sharon Hamilton.
  - Humanities in Society. Volume 1: Number 1. Los Angeles: University of Southern California Center for the Humanities, 1978. pp. 85. (Box 3, Folder 98)
    Edited by Ronald Gottesman and Jeffrey Plank.
    Contributions by Marshall Cohen, Ronald Berman and Nancy Struever.
    Article of note: "The Humanities and the Modern."
  - ICON Thoughtstyle Magazine. Issue One. New York: ICON, April 1997. pp. 128. (Box 3, Folder 99)
    Edited by David Getson.
    Contributions by Mark Bittman, Nat Hentoff and Colin McDowell.
    Article of note: "The Accidental Capitalist."
    Design by John W. Duffy.
  - Image: A Quarterly of the Visual Arts. Number One. London: Art and Technics, Summer 1949. pp. 84. (Box 3, Folder 100)
    Edited by Robert Harling.
    Contributions by Geoffrey Grigson, John Lewis and Stuart Rose.
    Article of note: "Book Illustrations by John Minton."
  - India Review. Volume One: Number One. London: Frank Cass, January 2002. pp. 124. (Box 3, Folder 101)
    Edited by Sumit Ganguly.
    Contributions by Rajeev Bhargava, Ainslie Embree and Gurpreet Mahajan.
    Article of note: "Indian Democracy: The Rule of Law on Trial."
  - Influence. Number One. New York: Influence, 2003. pp. 158. (Box 7, Folder 252)
    Edited by Raul Martinez and Jan-Willem Dikkers.
    Contributions by Kurt Andersen and Lawrence Weschler.
    Article of note: "City Without Qualities: Photography, Cinema, and the Postapocalyptic Ruin."
    Design by Michael Ian Kaye.
  - Innovation: Princeton Journal of Science and Technology. Volume One: Number One. Princeton: Princeton University, 2000. pp. 32. (Box 3, Folder 102)
    Edited by Abraham Crystal.
    Contributions by Philipp Bleek and Carl Riccadonna.
    Article of note: "Silicon Genome: Digital Revolution comes to Genetics."
    Design by Derek Djeu and Sarah Edwards.
  - Insurance: A Collection of New Writing. Issue One. New York: Each Press, 2000. pp. 100. (Box 3, Folder 103)
    Edited by Kostas Anagnopolous and Chris Tokar.
    Contributions by Lydia Davis, Jennifer Martensen and Susan Wheeler.
    Article of note: "Excerpt from 'Think and Grow Joe'."
    Design by Diane Shaw.
  - International Journal of Group Tensions: An Interdisciplinary Quarterly of Behavioral Sciences Devoted to the Study of Conflict and Violence in Human Relations. Volume One: Number One. New York: Organization for the Study of Group Tensions, January–March 1971. pp. 104. (Box 3, Folder 104)
    Edited by Benjamin Wolman.
    Contributions by Morton Deutsch, Leonard Dobb and Roger Egeberg.
    Article of note: "White Anti-Black Prejudice in the United States."
  - International Journal of Infrared and Millimeter Waves. Volume One: Number One. New York: Plenum Publishing, March 1980. pp. 160. (Box 3, Folder 105)
    Edited by Kenneth J. Button.
    Contributions by D. M. Bolle, A. V. Nurmikko and S. Talisa.
    Article of note: "Generation of Ultrashort Pulses in Synchronous Pumping of Near-Millimeter Wave Lasers."
  - International Journal of Oral History. Volume One: Number One. Westport, Connecticut: Meckler Publishing, February 1980. pp. 84. (Box 3, Folder 106)
    Edited by Ronald Grele.
    Contributions by E. Culpepper Clark, Michael Hyde and Eva McMahan.
    Article of note: "Italian Working Class Culture Between the Wars: Consensus to Fascism and Work Ideology."
  - Inventario: Tutto é Progetto/Everything is a Project. Issue ˚01. Milan: Corraini, 2010. pp. 160. (Box 3, Folder 107)
    Edited by Beppe Finessi. Contributions by Pierluigi Anselmi, Marco Manini and Mariana Siracus.
    Article of note: "Near Future."
    Design by Artemio Croatto, Designwork.
  - Investment Outlook. Volume 1: Number 1. New York: Argus Publishing, July 15, 1933. pp. 4. (Box 7, Folder 253)
    Contribution by George M. Bemis, Jr.
    Article of note: "General Foods Corporation, An Industrial with Good Earnings and Liberal Dividends."
  - Jetrosexual. Volume One. Virgin Atlantic Airways, 2004. pp. 46. (Box 3, Folder 108)
    Contributions by Israel Baron, Lisa Campbell and Phil Keoghan.
    Article of note: "Meet, Greet, Change the World."
  - Joe. Volume 1: Number 1. New York: Time Inc. Custom Publishing, 1999. pp. 84. (Box 3, Folder 109)
    Edited by Scott Mowbray.
    Contributions by Geof Kern, Jan Meissner and Douglas Coupland.
    Article of note: "Trust Me."
    Design by Lloyd Ziff.
  - Journal of African Business. Volume One: Number One. Binghamton, New York: International Business Press, 2000. pp. 132. (Box 3, Folder 110)
    Edited by Sam Okoroafo.
    Contributions by Albert Alos, Terence Nevitt and Autuan Perry.
    Article of note: "Aligning Private Development and Economic Growth in Nigeria.
  - Journal de Nimes. Number 1. The Blue Issue. Amsterdam: Tenue de Nimes, May 2009. pp. 23. (Box 3, Folder 111)
    Edited by Samuel Wesley.
    Contributions by Menno Van Meurs, Philip Goss and Joanna Van Unen.
    Article of note: "History Made by Lee." Design by Tenue de Nîmes.
  - Journal of Anthropological Archeology. Volume 1: Number 1. New York: Academic Press, March 1982. pp. 118. (Box 3, Folder 112)
    Edited by Robert Whallon.
    Contributions by Brad Bartel, Lewis R. Binford and James R. Sackett.
    Article of note: "The Archeology of Place."
  - Journal of Applied Animal Welfare Science. Volume 1: Number 1. Mahwah, New Jersey: Lawrence Erlbaum, 1998. pp. 94. (Box 3, Folder 113)
    Edited by Kenneth Shapiro and Stephen Zawistowski.
    Contributions by Andrzej Elzanowski, Roger Fouts and Richard Ryder.
    Article of note: "Destructible Toys as Enrichment for Captive Chimpanzees."
  - Journal of Cold War Studies. Volume 1: Number 1. Cambridge, Massachusetts: Davis Center for Russian Studies, Harvard University, Winter 1999. pp. 124. (Box 3, Folder 114)
    Edited by Mark Kramer.
    Contributions by Francis Gavin, Nigel Gould-Davies and Adam B. Ulam.
    Article of note: "Politics, Power and US Policy in Iran, 1950-1953."
  - Journal of Crop Production: Innovations in Practice, Theory & Research. Volume 1: Number 1. Binghamton, New York: Haworth Press, 1998. pp. 308. (Box 3, Folder 115)
    Edited by Amarjit Basra.
    Contributions by Douglas Buhler, T.S. Cox and Lianzheng Wang.
    Article of note: "The Changing Global Environment and World Crop Production."
  - The Journal of Higher Education. Volume 1: Number 1. Columbus: Ohio State University Press, January 1930. pp. 64. (Box 3, Folder 116)
    Edited by W. W. Charters.
    Contributions by John G. Bowman, Robert M. Hutchins and Carl E. Seashore.
    Article of note: "The Spirit of the University of Chicago."
  - Journal of Homosexuality. Volume 1: Number 1. New York: Haworth Press, Fall 1974. pp. 144. (Box 3, Folder 117)
    Edited by Charles Silverstein.
    Contributions by Richard Games and A.P. MacDonald.
    Article of note: "Characteristics of Those Who Hold Positive and Negative Attitudes Toward Homosexuals."
  - Journal of Internet Cataloging: International Quarterly of Digital Organization, Classification and Access. Volume 1: Number 1. Binghamton, New York: Haworth Press, 1997. pp. 92. (Box 3, Folder 118)
    Edited by Ruth Carter and Roger Brisson.
    Contributions by Cecily Johns, Gerry McKiernan and Susan Neumeister.
    Article of note: "Yahoo! Cataloging the Web."
  - Journal of Machine Learning Research. Volume One: Number One. Cambridge, Massachusetts: MIT Press, Winter 2001. pp. 78. (Box 3, Folder 119)
    Edited by Leslie Kaelbing.
    Contributions by Michael Jordan and Marine Meila.
    Article of note: "Networks for Inference, Collaborative Filtering and Data Visualization."
  - Journal of Modern Literature. Volume One: Number One. Philadelphia: Temple University, 1970. pp. 146. (Box 3, Folder 120)
    Edited by Maurice Beebe.
    Contributions by Kenneth B. Newell, Sy Kahn and Marjorie Perloff.
    Article of note: "The Destructive Element and Related 'Dream' Passages in the Lord Jim Manuscript."
    Cover art by Saul Field.
  - Journal of Pragmatics: An Interdisciplinary Quarterly of Language Studies. Volume One: Number One. Amsterdam: North-Holland Publishing, April 1977. pp. 106. (Box 3, Folder 121)
    Edited by Jacob Mey and Hartmut Haberland.
    Contributions by Ulrich Ammon and Dieter Wunderlich.
    Article of note: "Methodological Questions About Artificial Intelligence Approaches to Understanding Natural Language."
  - Journal of the Printing Historical Society. New Series: Number One. London: Printing Historical Society, Summer 2000. pp. 88. (Box 3, Folder 122)
    Edited by Richard Lawrence and Christopher Burke.
    Contributions by John Flood, Robin Kinross and Michael Twyman.
    Article of note: "On Gutenberg's 600th Anniversary: Towards A History of Jubilees of Printing."
    Design by Christopher Burke.
  - The Journal of the Shivas Irons Society: Golf, Literature, Art. Number One. Carmel, California: The Shivas Irons Society, 2004. pp. 80., 2000 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    Edited by Will McCulloch.
    Contributions by Bernard Darwin, Bradley S. Klein and Timothy Walsh.
    Article of note: "Myth, History, and the Sense of Place."
    Design by Tom Ingalls, Stephen Turner and Ed O'Brien.
  - Journal of Social Entrepreneurship. Volume 1: Number 1. Oxon, England: Taylor & Francis, 2010. pp. 170. (Box 3, Folder 124)
    Edited by Alex Nicholls.
    Contributions by Matthew Shea, Brett Smith, Paul N. Bloom, Nuria Toledano and Jacques Defourny.
    Article of note: "Converting Failed Financial Institutions into Mutual Organisations."
  - Journal of Threat Assessment. Volume One: Number One. Binghamton, New York; Haworth Press, 2001. pp. 110. (Box 3, Folder 125)
    Edited by Joseph McCann.
    Contributions by Gerald Cooke, Tom Mason and Louis Schlesinger.
    Article of note: "Risk Factors for Violence Among Stalkers."
  - The Journal of Typographic Research. Volume One: Number One. Cleveland: Western Reserve University, January 1967. pp. 112. (Box 3, Folder 126)
    Edited by Merald E. Wrolstad.
    Contributions by Edward Fry, J. H. Prince and Richard H. Wiggins.